Their Music Made Them Famous, Their Lives Made Them Infamous.
The Dirt is a drama, music, comedy film directed by Jeff Tremaine.
The story of Mötley Crüe and their rise from the Sunset Strip
club scene of the early 1980s to superstardom.
Tommy Lee, played by mgk.
Nikki Sixx, played by Douglas Booth.
Vince Neil, played by Daniel Webber.
Mick Mars, played by Iwan Rheon.
Tom Zutaut, played by Pete Davidson.
Doc McGhee, played by David Costabile.
The Dirt is a 2019 American biographical comedy-drama film directed by Jeff Tremaine and written
by Rich Wilkes and Amanda Adelson, about heavy metal/glam metal band Mötley Crüe.
The film stars Douglas Booth, Colson Baker, Daniel Webber and Iwan Rheon.
Talks of a Mötley Crüe biopic began as early as 2006, when Paramount Pictures and MTV Films purchased the rights to the book The Dirt: Confessions of the World's Most Notorious Rock Band by the band and
Neil Strauss; however, the project then languished in development hell for over a decade, going through numerous directors and cast members before Netflix purchased the rights in March 2017.
Filming began around New Orleans in February 2018.
The Dirt was released digitally on Netflix on March 22, 2019.
It received generally negative reviews from critics, who said the film would please fans but
that it hesitated "in handling the more troubling aspects of the band's history."
The film explores themes of drug addiction, 1980s, hair metal, metal band.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.